<resources>
    <string name="app_name">IELTS Assistor</string>
    <string name="fetching_tip_please_wait">Fetching Tip Please Wait</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="welcome_to_know_your_band_score">Welcome to know your band score!!!</string>
    <string name="listening">Listening:</string>
    <string name="reading">Reading:</string>
    <string name="writing">Writing:</string>
    <string name="speaking">Speaking:</string>
    <string name="infoOnAttention">- It is a very common situation on IELTS Listening when a speaker gives some wrong information, then corrects himself and gives right information. This little trick is called <b>distraction</b>. You can get distracted by the information you hear the first time, thinking that it is correct. And that’s where a lot of IELTS candidates get caught! The speaker will then correct what he/she said, and give new information, which will be the right answer. Let\'s look at the examples below. Listen to the audio and answer the questions. You\'ve also given a transcript with an <u>underlined answer</u>.<b>Now listen carefully and answer the two questions by applying this tricks</b></string>
    <string name="AttentionQstn1">Qstn 1: does a woman have any dietary restrictions?</string>
    <string name="clickAttentionQstn2">Qstn :2 - write down the phone number</string>
    <string name="tips1ForDistraction"> 1. <b>Listen</b> carefully even if you’ve heard the answer: it may be corrected and the right answer will come afterwards.</string>
    <string name="tips2ForDistraction">  2. <b>Pay attention</b> to words-indicators: <b>“no”, “sorry”, “mistake”</b>. These words indicate that the wrong answer will be corrected soon.</string>
    <string name="tips3ForDistraction">  3. <b> Keep in mind</b> that such distractions are very common for Part 1 of the listening test.</string>
    <string name="tips4ForDistraction">  4. <b>Be careful</b> when you hear <b>numbers or names</b>: they often get corrected.</string>
    <string name="AttentionQstn4"><b>Question 4: </b>Listen to the audio and answer the question below. Write <b>ONLY ONE NUMBER.</b></string>
    <string name="endingMessage">That\'s the end of Attention drawing Training! Now, apply these tricks while solving Cambridge Books. BEST OF LUCK</string>
    <string name="endingMessage2">That\'s the end of Scan Listening Questions Training! Now, apply these tricks while solving Cambridge Books. BEST OF LUCK</string>
    <string name="endingMessage3">That\'s the end of Listening MCQ Question Training! Now, apply these tricks while solving Cambridge Books. BEST OF LUCK</string>
    <string name="OverviewReadingQstnCarefully">To succeed in IELTS Listening, you should be very attentive. In this lesson we’ll train to read IELTS Listening questions carefully and avoid simple mistakes caused by lack of attention. Although this may sound too simple for you, in fact it’s very important to learn to read the questions carefully. <i>Quite often test-takers lose marks because they have read the question inattentively.</i></string>
    <string name="OverviewMCQ"><b>Multiple choice questions</b> commonly occur in parts 2, 3 and 4 of IELTS Listening test.  In such questions you are given three (rarely four) answer choices, only one of which is correct.
In this lesson you will learn <b>useful strategies and advice</b> to answer multiple choice questions in IELTS Listening test most effectively. You will also practice gained skills by answering tricky exercises with multiple choice questions.
The transcript is provided for each audio. The correct answers are underlined in the transcripts. For the examples the transcript is shown, and for the exercises it is hidden. You can hide/show the transcripts as you wish.
First, let’s learn some basic answering strategies and look at the examples below.
</string>
    <string name="tipsReadingQstnCarefully"><b><u>Tips: To avoid such mistakes, make sure you:</u></b></string>
    <string name="tip1ReadingQstn">1. Write words if you’re asked to write words, and write numbers if you’re asked to write numbers.</string>
    <string name="tip2ReadingQstn">2. Don’t exceed the word limit.</string>
    <string name="tip3ReadingQstn">3. Answer the question with relevant information</string>
    <string name="strategy1"><b><u>Strategy 1: don’t immediately pick up the first answer choice you hear.</u></b>
You will often hear all of the answer choices in the audio. And only one of them is correct, the other two are meant to confuse you! So don’t straightaway choose the answer you hear the first as it may be incorrect. So listen carefully and wait until the speaker finishes giving information about the current question.
Let’s try to use this strategy in the first example.
</string>
    <string name="strategy2"><b><u>Strategy 2: know that answers may come in a different order.</u>
    Unlike other questions types in IELTS Listening, multiple choice questions don’t necessarily have their answer choices
        coming in the same order as you hear them in the audio. So don’t worry if you first hear the third answer choice
        - it doesn’t mean you’ve missed the previous two, as answers often come in a different order.
    </b></string>

    <string name="strategy3"><b><u>Strategy 3:  mind that answers are often paraphrased..</u>
   You shouldn’t be waiting for a 100% match - the answer choice can differ from what you hear as it can be paraphrased.
        To approach multiple choice questions effectively, look through the answer choices while listening to the question
        being discussed. Do it to get a general idea of answer choices.
    </b></string>

    <string name="explanationMCQ1"><b>Answer is incorrect</b>\n<b>Explanation:</b> As you can hear, all three answer choices were mentioned.
        However, the first two of them (“all alone” and “sitting on the ground”) are clearly incorrect,
        because the speakers say that people often think that if a bird is all alone or sitting on the ground it
        needs to be rescued, but it’s just learning to fly. The last sentence the speaker says gives us the correct answer:
        “So we should emphasize that people should only attempt to rescue a bird that’s clearly injured”.
        So the correct answer is <b>C.</b></string>

    <string name="explanationMCQ2"><b>Explanation:</b>Moreover, the synonyms are used! The speaker gives the correct answer
        when she says, “In fact, the best way of protection is preventing the disease by keeping yourself clean and washing
        hands before you eat”. But instead of keeping yourself clean or washing hands we have a paraphrased answer choice
        - following hygiene rules. So, the right answer is <b>A</b>.Beware that paraphrase is often used in such questions,
        so you shouldn’t always look for an exact match.</string>

    <string-array name="tfActionName">
        <item>Useful Tips</item>
        <item>Passage 1</item>
        <item>Passage 2</item>
        <item>Passage 3</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="tfPassagesList">
        <item>More than ten years ago, while taking the temperature of the universe, astronomers found something odd.
            They discovered that a patch of sky, spanning the width of 20 moons, was unusually cold.
            The astronomers were measuring the thermal radiation that bathes the entire universe,
            a glowing relic of the big bang.To gaze at this cosmic microwave background,
            or CMB, is to glimpse the primordial1 universe, a time when it was less than 400,000 years old.
            The CMB blankets the sky, and looks pretty much the same everywhere,
            existing at a feebly cold temperature of 2.725 kelvins -
            just a couple degrees warmer than absolute zero.
            But armed with the newly launched WMAP satellite,
            the astronomers had set out to probe temperature variations as tiny as one part in 100,000.
            Born from the quantum froth that was the universe a half-moment after the big bang,
            those random fluctuations help scientists understand what the cosmos is made of and how it all came to be.</item>
        <item>According to the Met Office, the UK had its warmest July day ever on July 1, when temperatures hit 36.7 C near London.
            There were record heat waves in many countries including Spain, while the African continent had the second-warmest July
            on record. While the impact of increased levels of carbon dioxide in the atmosphere is a key driver of rising
            temperatures, another important factor is El Nino. This natural phenomenon, which appears as a large swathe of warm
            water in the Pacific every few years, is known to push up global temperatures. In recent days there have been reports
            that this year\'s El Nino will be particularly intense. As a result, many experts believe that 2015 will be the warmest
            year on record by some margin. The seas have also been soaking up a large amount of heat, the NOAA said, with record
            warming in large expanses of the Pacific and Indian Oceans Peter Stott, head of climate monitoring and attribution at
            the UK Met Office, said: \"A strong El Nino is under way in the tropical Pacific and this, combined with the long-term
            global warming trend, means there is the potential to see some very warm months throughout this year - as the new
            figures for July appear to show\".
        </item>
        <item>
            The standard stereotype among Americans is that Canadians are like Americans, except they say \'eh\' a lot and pronounce \'out and about\' as \'oot and aboot\'. Many Canadians, on the other hand, will tell you that Canadian English is more like British English, and as proof will hold aloft the spellings colour and centre and the name zed for the letter Z.
  Canadian does exist as a separate variety of British English, with subtly distinctive features of pronunciation and vocabulary. It has its own dictionaries; the Canadian Press has its own style guide; the Editors\' Association of Canada has just released a second edition of Editing Canadian English. But an emblematic feature of Editing Canadian English is comparison tables of American versus British spellings so the Canadian editor can come to a reasonable decision on which to use… on each occasion. The core of Canadian English is a pervasive ambivalence.
  Canadian history helps to explain this. In the beginning there were the indigenous people, with far more linguistic and cultural variety than Europe. They\'re still there, but Canadian English, like Canadian Anglophone society in general, gives them little more than desultory token nods. Fights between European settlers shaped Canadian English more. The French, starting in the 1600s, colonised the St Lawrence River region and the Atlantic coast south of it. In the mid-1700s, England got into a war with France, concluding with the Treaty of Paris in 1763, which ceded \'New France\' to England. The English allowed any French to stay who were willing to become subjects of the English King.
  At the time of the Treaty of Paris, however, there were very few English speakers in Canada. The American Revolution changed that. The founding English-speaking people of Canada were United Empire Loyalists – people who fled American independence and were rewarded with land in Canada. Thus, Canadian English was, from its very beginning, both American – because its speakers had come from the American colonies – and not American, because they rejected the newly independent nation.
  Just as the Americans sought to have a truly distinct, independent American version of English, the loyalists sought to remain more like England… sort of. These were people whose variety of English was already diverging from the British and vice versa: when the residents of London and its environs began to drop their r\'s and change some of their vowels people in certain parts of the United States adopted some of these changes, but Canadians did not. </item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="details">
        <item><b>IELTS</b>- International English Language Testing System: It is widely recognized as
            a standard of testing the language ability of candidates who need to study or work where English
            is used as a medium of communication. It is owned by three partners: the University of Cambridge -
            LIFE ESOL Examinations, the British Council and the IDP: Education Australia.
            <n><b>Test Format</b></n>
            IELTS consists of six modules. All candidates take the same Listening and Speaking modules.
            There is a choice of – Reading and Writing modules to whether an examinee is taking the Academic
            or the General version of the Test.
            <b>Academic</b>: For candidates taking the test for entry to undergraduate or postgraduate studies
            or for professional reasons.
            <b>General Training</b>: For candidates taking the test for entry to vocational or training programs
            not at degree level, for admission secondary schools and for immigration purposes.
            The test modules are taken in the following order:
            <n><b><u>LISTENING</u></b></n>
            <b>4 sections, 40 items, approximately 30 minutes </b>(additional 10 minutes to transfer the answers on an answer sheet)
             <n><b><u>ACADEMIC READING:</u></b></n>
            <b>3 passages, 40 items, 60 minutes</b>
            or, <n><b><u>GENERAL TRAINING READING: </u></b></n>
            <b>3 sections, 40 items, 60 minutes</b>
            <n><b><u>ACADEMIC WRITING:</u></b></n>
            <b>2 tasks, 60 minutes</b>
            or, <n><b><u>GENERAL TRAINING WRITING:</u></b></n>
            <b>2 tasks, 60 minutes</b>


            <n><u><b></b>SPEAKING:</u></n>
            <b>11 -14 minutes</b>
            <b><u>Total test time: 2 hours 44 minutes</u></b>
        </item>
        <item>
            <n><b>Paper format:</b></n>
            There are four sections with ten questions each. The questions are designed so that the answers
            appear in the order they are heard in the audio. The first two sections deal with situations set
            in everyday social contexts. In Section 1, there is a conversation between two speakers
            (for example, a conversation about travel arrangements), and in Section 2, there is a monologue
            in (for example, a speech about local facilities). The final two sections deal with situations set
            in educational and training contexts. In Section 3, there is a conversation between two main speakers
            (for example, two university students in discussion, perhaps guided by a tutor), and in Section 4,
            there is a monologue on an academic subject. The recordings are heard only once. They include a range
            of accents, including British, Australian, New Zealand, American and Canadian
            <b>Timing:</b> Approximately 30 minutes (plus 10 minutes transfer time)
            <b>No. of questions:</b> 40



            <b>Task types:</b>
            A variety of question types are used chosen from the following:

            •	multiple choice
            •	matching
            •	plan/map/diagram labeling
            •	form/note/table/flow-chart/summary completion
            •	Sentence completion.
            <b>Answering System</b>
            Test takers write their answers on the question paper as they listen and at the end of the test are given
            10 minutes to transfer their answers to an answer sheet. Care should be taken when writing answers on the
            answer sheet as poor spelling and grammar are penalized.

        </item>
        <item>
           <n><b>Paper format:</b></n>
            There are three reading passages with a variety of questions using a number of task types.
            <b><n>Task types:</n></b>
            A variety of question types are used, chosen from the following; multiple choice,
            identifying information, identifying the writer’s views/claims, matching information,
            matching headings, matching features, matching sentence endings, sentence completion,
            summary completion, note completion, table completion, flow-chart completion, diagram label completion
            and short-answer questions.
            <b><n>Sources</n></b>
            Texts are taken from books, journals, magazines and newspapers, and have been written for a non-specialist audience.
            All the topics are of general interest. They deal with issues which are interesting,
            recognizably appropriate and accessible to test takers entering undergraduate or postgraduate courses
            or seeking professional registration. The passages may be written in a variety of styles, for example narrative,
            descriptive or discursive/argumentative. At least one text contains detailed logical argument.
            Texts may contain non-verbal materials such as diagrams, graphs or illustrations.
            If texts contain technical terms a simple glossary is provided.
            <b><n>Answering</n></b>
            Test takers are required to transfer their answers to an answer sheet during the time allowed for the test.
            No extra time is allowed for transfer. Care should be taken when writing answers on the answer sheet as poor
            spelling and grammar are penalized.

            <n>Marks: Each question is worth 1 mark.</n>

        </item>
        <item>
           <n><b>Paper format:</b></n>
            <n>There are two Writing tasks and BOTH must be completed.
            Task types: In Task 1, test takers are asked to describe some visual information
            (graph/table/chart/diagram) in their own words. They need to write 150 words in about 20 minutes.
            In Task 2, they respond to a point of view or argument or problem. They need to write 250 words
            in about 40 minutes.</n>
            <b>Answering:</b>
            <n>
            Answers must be given on the answer sheet and must be written in full.
            Notes or bullet points are not acceptable as answers. Test takers may write on the question paper
            but this cannot be taken from the examination room and will not be seen by the examiner.</n>
        Marks: <b>Band score 9 on individual task, from task 1, 40% marks and from task 2,
            60% marks will be counted and then, both are summed to get a overall band in writing.</b>
        </item>
        <item>
            <n><b>Paper format:</b></n>
            The Speaking test consists of an oral interview between the test takers and an examiner.
            All Speaking tests are recorded.
            <b>Task types:</b>
            <n>There are three parts to the test and each part fulfils a specific function in terms of interaction pattern,
            task input and test takers output.In part one, examiner asks some basic questions about candidates - name, interest
            etc. In the second part, candidates will get an cue card, then s/he will have to talk about the topic on the
            cue card for around 2 minutes. There will be some time to jot down some notes about the given topic.Finally, in the
            last part, examiner will ask about more abstract issues which are thematically linked to topic in part 2. Total time
            for speaking test is approximately 15-20 minutes.</n>
            Marks: test takers are scored on the basis of band score 9.

        </item>
        <item>
            <n><b>Listening Score calculation</b></n>
            <n>Listenig scores are calculated by the number of correct answers a candidate scores out of 40 questions. No
            point loss for wrong answers.</n>
            <n><b>Correct answers    -     Band Scores</b></n>
            <n><b>   39-40           -     9          </b></n>
            <n><b>   37-38           -     8.5          </b></n>
            <n><b>   35-36           -     8          </b></n>
            <n><b>   32-34           -     7.5         </b></n>
            <n><b>   30-31           -     7          </b></n>
            <n><b>   26-29           -     6.5         </b></n>
            <n><b>   23-25           -     6          </b></n>
            <n><b>   18-22           -     5.5          </b></n>
            <n><b>   16-17           -     5           </b></n>
            <n><b>   13-15           -     4.5          </b></n>
            <n><b>   11-12           -     4          </b></n>
            <n><b>   8-10            -     3.5          </b></n>
            <n><b>   6-7             -     3          </b></n>
            <n><b>   3-5             -     2.5          </b></n>

            <n><b>Reading Score calculation</b></n>
            <n>Readnig scores are also calculated by the number of correct answers a candidate scores out of 40 questions. No
            point loss for wrong answers.</n>
            <n><b>Correct answers    -     Band Scores</b></n>
            <n><b>   39-40           -     9          </b></n>
            <n><b>   37-38           -     8.5          </b></n>
            <n><b>   35-36           -     8          </b></n>
            <n><b>   33-34           -     7.5         </b></n>
            <n><b>   30-32           -     7          </b></n>
            <n><b>   27-29           -     6.5         </b></n>
            <n><b>   23-26           -     6          </b></n>
            <n><b>   19-22           -     5.5          </b></n>
            <n><b>   15-18           -     5           </b></n>
            <n><b>   13-14           -     4.5          </b></n>
            <n><b>   10-12           -     4          </b></n>
            <n><b>   8-9             -     3.5          </b></n>
            <n><b>   6-7             -     3          </b></n>
            <n><b>   3-5             -     2.5          </b></n>

        <b>Band score: </b> All IELTS scores from 0 to 9. In each skill, candidates get score and then have an overview bandscore
            which is the avarage of all scores.

        </item>

    </string-array>

    <string name="sc_passage_1">
        "Congenital heart experts from Spectrum Health Helen DeVos Children's Hospital have "
            "successfully integrated two common imaging techniques to produce"
            "a three-dimensional anatomic model of a patient's heart."
            "\n\n"
            " The 3D model printing of patients' hearts has become more common in recent years as part of an emerging, "
            "experimental field devoted to enhanced visualization of individual cardiac structures and characteristics."
            "But this is the first time the integration of computed tomography (CT) and three-dimensional transesophageal"
            " echocardiography (3DTEE) has successfully been used for printing a hybrid 3D model of a patient's heart. "
            "A proof-of-concept study authored by the Spectrum Health experts also opens the way for these techniques"
            "to be used in combination with a third tool\n"
            "\n"
            " - magnetic resonance imaging (MRI).\n"
            "\n"
            " \"Hybrid 3D printing integrates the best aspects of two or more imaging modalities,"
            " which can potentially enhance diagnosis, as well as interventional and surgical planning,"
            "\" said Jordan Gosnell, Helen DeVos Children's Hospital cardiac sonographer,"
            " and lead author of the study. \"Previous methods of 3D printing utilize only one imaging modality, "
            "which may not be as accurate as merging two or more datasets.\""
    </string>
    <string name="sc_passage_2">
          About a quarter of the world\'s population could have worms living in their guts. For many years experts have recommended treating large groups at risk of infection - but is this mass approach worthwhile?\n\n
  Evidence showing the benefits of large-scale deworming projects has come under scrutiny in recent weeks - the debate has even been dubbed \"worm wars\". Parasites, such as roundworm, hookworm and whipworm could be living inside more than 1.5 billion people according to the World Health Organization (WHO).\n\n
    People are usually infected through contaminated food but hookworm larvae can also burrow into feet, get into blood vessels and make their way to the heart and lungs. From there they can climb up to the oesophagus* and be swallowed, ending up in the gut where they grow.\n\n
  Worms are not usually fatal but in serious cases they can cause abdominal pain, diarrhoea, loss of appetite, weight loss, fatigue and anaemia. In children, they can also contribute to malnutrition, stunted growth, and absences from school. A nurse gives deworming treatment to a boy in India\n\n
*oesophagus - throat\n

    </string>
    <string name="sc_passage_3">
          Keepers at the Smithsonian National Zoo in Washington DC only discovered Mei Xiang was pregnant during an ultrasound scan last week. The zoo said both cubs appeared healthy. Giant pandas are one of the most endangered species in the world and are notoriously hard to breed in captivity.\n\n
  The National Zoo is one of only four zoos in the US to have pandas, which are on loan from China. Mei Xiang, who has two other offspring, is one of the zoo\'s star attractions and a Panda Cam on her enclosure crashed within seconds of the birth of the first cub being announced because of the volume of interest.\n\n
  Female pandas are able to conceive for only two or three days a year, leading to a very low reproduction rate. Mei Xiang was artificially inseminated with sperm from the zoo\'s resident male Tian Tian and a panda named Hui Hui from Wolong, China. It will not be known for a while which is the father, or what sex the cubs are.\n\n
  It has previously taken months before Mei Xiang\'s cubs have been introduced to the public. AP news agency reports that her first cub, Tai Shan, was born in 2005 and returned to China in 2010; her second cub, Bao Bao, is two years old on Sunday and still lives at the zoo. The panda population is threatened by habitat loss as land is increasingly inhabited by humans, with about 1,800 pandas left in the wild in China. However, the number living in the wild in China has gone up over the last 10 years.\n

    </string>

    <string-array name="sc_passage_list">
        <item>@string/sc_passage_1</item>
        <item>@string/sc_passage_2</item>
        <item>@string/sc_passage_3</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="sc_question_set_1">
        1. A three-dimensional __________ of a patient\'s heart was created by integrating two imaging techniques.\n\n
        2.Spectrum Health scientists have found a way to combine and use three techniques: computed tomography,
        three-dimensional transesophageal echocardiography and _______.\n\n
        3.The new method of 3D printing is more efficient than previous methods because it merges
            two and more _______.\n\n
        4.With more accurate 3D renderings and ______, \n
        physicians will be able to better diagnose and treat heart disease.\n
    </string>

    <string name="sc_question_set_2">
        1.	Now scientists doubt whether it is _________ to treat large groups of possibly infected people.\n\n
        2.	The experts called the debate _________ .\n\n
        3.	Hookworm larvae might make his way to the _________ and then be swallowed.\n\n
        4.	Although dangerous, worms are rarely _________ .\n
    </string>

    <string name="sc_question_set_3">
        1.	Mei Xiang pregnancy was discovered with an _________ last week.\n\n
        2.	Pandas from the USA National Zoo are _________ from China.\n\n
        3.	Due to the short conceiving period, pandas have a low ________ .\n\n
        4.	Pandas are in danger because their lands are increasingly _________ .\n
    </string>

    <string-array name="sc_question_list">
        <item>@string/sc_question_set_1</item>
        <item>@string/sc_question_set_2</item>
        <item>@string/sc_question_set_3</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="loh_paragraph_1">
        (A) Australia\'s wildlife is unique. The vast majority of the animals that live there are not
            " found anywhere else – and things were no different 1 million years ago during the Pleistocene:"
            " the age of the super-sized mammal. Before humanity became Earth's undisputed superpower,"
            " giant beasts of all shapes and sizes dominated every continent, but the Pleistocene mammals"
            " of Australia were different. Some of them could grow to the size of small cars, or possessed "
            " teeth longer than knife blades.\n"  "\n"
            " (B) None of these animals survive today – although exactly why that\'s the case is a mystery. Humans,"
            " with their advanced hunting techniques and use of fire to modify the landscape, may have played a"
            " central role in the megafauna\'s disappearance, but this idea is still a matter of heated debate.\n"  "\n"
            "(C.) Even if we cannot be sure that the arrival of Australian Aboriginals on the continent had catastrophic"
            " effects on its native animals, it seems that the animals had a rather spiritual effect on the humans. The"
            " Aboriginal mythological \"Dreamtime\" includes a cast of monstrous creatures, many of which bear a close"
            " resemblance to some of the real-life monsters that once stalked Australia\'s plains. Are the myths based"
            " in fact? Perhaps: after all, these creatures are far stranger than anything dreamed up by humans.\n"
            "\n"
            "(D) For instance, the two-tonnes weighting Diprotodon comfortably holds the title of largest marsupial ever."
            " In size and appearance it looked superficially like a modern rhinoceros, but the Diprotodon seems to have"
            "had a social lifestyle more like that of an elephant, another mammal with which it shares anatomical "
            "similarities. What the Diprotodon most resembles, however, is exactly what it is: an enormous wombat."
            "\n"
            "(E) Another record breaker, this time a world champion; Varanus priscus, commonly known by its antiquated"
            " genus name Megalania – was the largest terrestrial lizard the world has ever known. Megalania was a goanna"
            " lizard, a relative of today\'s infamous Komodo dragon, and conservative estimates have predicted that it was"
            " at least 5.5m long.\n"
            "\n"
            "(F) These monster marsupials were not the only giants. Their numbers were swelled by half-tonne birds"
            " and dinosaur-like tortoises. Although this biological assemblage was truly nightmarish for humans, it"
            " greatly enriched the Australia\’s fauna and contributed to the world\’s biological diversity. Unfortunately,"
            " all of these species are extinct nowadays. This fact shows us that even strong, monstrous creatures can"
            " easily die out. So we need to care about animals that surround us today and don\’t let them disappear as "
            " it happened to their distant ancestors."
    </string>
    <string name="loh_passage_2">
        A. The Yoruba people of Nigeria classify their towns in two ways. Permanent towns with their own governments are called \“ilu\”, whereas temporary settlements, set up to support work in the country are \“aba\”. Although ilu tend to be larger than aba, the distinction is not one of size, some aba are large, while declining ilu can be small, but of purpose. There is no \“typical\” Yoruba town, but some features are common to most towns.\n\n
B. In the 19th century most towns were heavily fortified and the foundations of these walls are sometimes visible. Collecting tolls to enter and exit through the walls was a major source of revenue for the old town rulers, as were market fees. The markets were generally located centrally and in small towns, while in large towns there were permanent stands made of corrugated iron or concrete. The market was usually next to the local ruler\’s palace.\n\n
C. The palaces were often very large. In the 1930\’s, the area of Oyo\’s palace covered 17 acres, and consisted of a series of courtyards surrounded by private and public rooms. After colonisation, many of the palaces were completely or partially demolished. Often the rulers built two storey houses for themselves using some of the palace grounds for government buildings.\n\n
D. The town is divided into different sections. In some towns these are regular, extending out from the center of the town like spokes on a wheel, while in others, where space is limited, they are more random. The different areas are further divided into compounds called \“ile\”. These vary in size considerably from single dwellings to up to thirty houses. They tend to be larger in the North. Large areas are devoted to government administrative buildings. Newer developments such as industrial or commercial areas or apartment housing for civil servants tends to be build on the edge of the town.\n\n
E. Houses are rectangular and either have a courtyard in the center or the rooms come off a central corridor. Most social life occurs in the courtyard. They are usually built of hardened mud and have roofs of corrugated iron or, in the countryside, thatch. Buildings of this material are easy to alter, either by knocking down rooms or adding new ones. And can be improved by coating the walls with cement. Richer people often build their houses of concrete blocks and, if they can afford to, build two storey houses. Within compounds there can be quite a mixture of building types. Younger well-educated people may have well furnished houses while their older relatives live in mud walled buildings and sleep on mats on the floor.\n\n
F. The builder or the most senior man gets a room either near the entrance or, in a two storied house, next to the balcony. He usually has more than one room. Junior men get a room each and there are separate rooms for teenage boys and girls to sleep in. Younger children sleep with their mothers. Any empty room are used as storage, let out or, if they face the street, used as shops.\n</string>

    <string name="loh_passage_3">
        (A) With upwards of 300 product launches, installations and exhibitions, London\'s annual nine-day design festival is a showcase of head-spinning choice. In many ways that\'s the beauty of the extravaganza, everyone has a different experience and takes something unique away from it. There were however some intriguing themes and trends in this year\'s edition that spoke to larger social or cultural preoccupations.

(B) One was the launch of two consumer electronics products designed to simplify and beautify our technology-addled lives. Both chose the new London Design Festival venue of Somerset House to show their wares. The first was a mobile phone launched by Swiss company Punkt and designed by Jasper Morrison that allows users to make calls and texts only (well, it has an alarm clock and an address book too). Punkt founder Petter Neby doesn\'t believe it will replace your smart phone but suggests users fit it with the same SIM card as your main phone and use it in the evenings, weekends and on holiday.

( C) The other electronics launch came from the unlikely French sibling duo of the Bouroullec brothers. Though tech companies like Samsung are usually prescriptive about their products the Bouroullecs (who admitted they found most TVs sad and ugly) seem to have been given free rein. Their new television for the mega Korean brand looks more like an item of furniture than an ultra-large and ultra-slim piece of tech. More importantly, it comes with simplified on-screen interaction and a \'curtain mode\' that turns your screen into a shimmering pattern during ads or half-time. Again, their focus was on dialing down digital insanity.

(D) Customizable online furniture was also very much in vogue at this year\'s festival. But rest assured, weird and unreliable software or off-the-wall designs sent to a 3D printer somewhere and arriving months later, seem to be a thing of the past. Customization may finally have come of age. Two examples were Scandi-brand Hem that combinded good design by the likes of Luca Nichetto, Form Us With Love and Sylvain Willenz with affordable price points. The fact that the brand opened a pop-up store in Covent Garden during the festival is a recognition of the importance of both physical and online spaces that work seamlessly together.

(E) Another online configurable brand to make its debut after years in development was Warsaw-based Tylko. Like Hem, Tylko has spent time and money on very powerful and easy-to-use software, but with only three designs - a table, a shelf and salt and pepper mills - it has a way to go. Its augmented reality app is simple to use however and its table has been developed with a nano-coating option that really does appear to keep pesky stains at bay. Craft and \'making\' in all its forms was once again a big hit and nowhere more so than at TENT, the East London design event that gets better every year.

(F) A definite highlight was the massive space taken over by the Design &amp; Crafts Council of Ireland and filled with weavers and potters doing their thing and showing their wares. Irish Design had another delectable stand over at the Rochelle School in East London too. The Souvenir Project was a series of nine non-cliché \'souvenirs\' made in Ireland and included a rainbow plate by Nicholas Mosse Pottery that featured rows of animals, flowers and watering cans and commemorated the legalization of same-sex marriage in Ireland in May 2015.
    </string>

    <string-array name="loh_passage_list">
        <item>@string/loh_paragraph_1</item>
        <item>@string/loh_passage_2</item>
        <item>@string/loh_passage_3</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="loh_headings_1">
        "i. Info on the largest mammal\n"
            "ii. Reference about Myths and reality \n"
            "iii. Incredible creatures of Pleistocene Australia \n"
            "iv. Importance of animal protection\n"
            "v. Giant lizards\n"
            "vi. \'Mystery the giants\' disappearance\n"
    </string>
    <string name="loh_headings_2">
        i.	Colonisation\n
        ii.	Urban divisions\n
        iii. Architectural home styles\n
        iv.	The residences of the rulers\n
        v.	Historical foundations\n
        vi.	Domestic arrangements\n
    </string>
    <string name="loh_headings_3">
         i.	Examples of customization\n
        ii.	Unusual keepsakes\n
        iii. A simple cell phone\n
        iv.	A strange TV\n
        v.	Number of products shown on the festival\n
        vi.	Three designs of a software\n
    </string>

    <string-array name="loh_heading_list">
        <item>@string/loh_headings_1</item>
        <item>@string/loh_headings_2</item>
        <item>@string/loh_headings_3</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="loh_solving_instruction">
        \nQuestions:\n
        \nThe reading passage has six paragraphs: i – vi.\n\n
        Choose the most suitable paragraph headings i – vi from the list of headings on the above.\n\n
        Select the appropriate numbers (i – vi) in the dropdown lists below
    </string>
    <string name="textView_loh_headings_title">Tips of List of Headings</string>
    
    <string name="loh_tips_strategy_string">
        1.	Quickly read through the paragraph headings so you can see what they say.\n
        2.	Then look at the first paragraph.\n
        3.	Often only the topic sentence needs to be read carefully because the main idea and answer are there - you may be able to just skim the rest.\n
        4.	Sometimes, however, the answer is not in the topic sentence and the whole paragraph needs to be read more carefully.\n
        5.	If a match is not immediately obvious, move on to the next one.\n
        6.	If you are unsure between two answers at first, put them both in. You may be able to eliminate one answer later if it fits another paragraph better.\n
        7.	If at the end you are still stuck between two answers for a question, pick which fits best.\n
    </string>

    <string name="loh_tips_beware_of_passage">
        1.	There are always more choices of paragraph headings on the list than paragraphs, so be careful when matching them.\n
        2.	Watch out for synonyms - often words in the paragraphs and paragraph headings will not be the same; they will be synonyms.\n
        3.	Having a noun from a heading that is in the paragraph does not guarantee they match - you still need to read it carefully to check.\n
    </string>
    <string name="btn_now_solve_a_passage">now solve a passage</string>
    <string name="strategies_to_answer_the_questions">Strategies to answer the questions</string>

</resources>
