<resources>
    <string name="app_name">IELTS Assistor</string>
    <string name="fetching_tip_please_wait">Fetching Tip Please Wait</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="welcome_to_know_your_band_score">Welcome to know your band score!!!</string>
    <string name="listening">Listening:</string>
    <string name="reading">Reading:</string>
    <string name="writing">Writing:</string>
    <string name="speaking">Speaking:</string>
    <string name="infoOnAttention">- It is a very common situation on IELTS Listening when a speaker gives some wrong information, then corrects himself and gives right information. This little trick is called <b>distraction</b>. You can get distracted by the information you hear the first time, thinking that it is correct. And that’s where a lot of IELTS candidates get caught! The speaker will then correct what he/she said, and give new information, which will be the right answer. Let\'s look at the examples below. Listen to the audio and answer the questions. You\'ve also given a transcript with an <u>underlined answer</u>.<b>Now listen carefully and answer the two questions by applying this tricks</b></string>
    <string name="AttentionQstn1">Qstn 1: does a woman have any dietary restrictions?</string>
    <string name="clickAttentionQstn2">Qstn :2 - write down the phone number</string>
    <string name="tips1ForDistraction"> 1. <b>Listen</b> carefully even if you’ve heard the answer: it may be corrected and the right answer will come afterwards.</string>
    <string name="tips2ForDistraction">  2. <b>Pay attention</b> to words-indicators: <b>“no”, “sorry”, “mistake”</b>. These words indicate that the wrong answer will be corrected soon.</string>
    <string name="tips3ForDistraction">  3. <b> Keep in mind</b> that such distractions are very common for Part 1 of the listening test.</string>
    <string name="tips4ForDistraction">  4. <b>Be careful</b> when you hear <b>numbers or names</b>: they often get corrected.</string>
    <string name="AttentionQstn4"><b>Question 4: </b>Listen to the audio and answer the question below. Write <b>ONLY ONE NUMBER.</b></string>
    <string name="endingMessage">That\'s the end of Attention drawing Training! Now, apply these tricks while solving Cambridge Books. BEST OF LUCK</string>
    <string name="endingMessage2">That\'s the end of Scan Listening Questions Training! Now, apply these tricks while solving Cambridge Books. BEST OF LUCK</string>
    <string name="endingMessage3">That\'s the end of Listening MCQ Question Training! Now, apply these tricks while solving Cambridge Books. BEST OF LUCK</string>
    <string name="OverviewReadingQstnCarefully">To succeed in IELTS Listening, you should be very attentive. In this lesson we’ll train to read IELTS Listening questions carefully and avoid simple mistakes caused by lack of attention. Although this may sound too simple for you, in fact it’s very important to learn to read the questions carefully. <i>Quite often test-takers lose marks because they have read the question inattentively.</i></string>
    <string name="OverviewMCQ"><b>Multiple choice questions</b> commonly occur in parts 2, 3 and 4 of IELTS Listening test.  In such questions you are given three (rarely four) answer choices, only one of which is correct.
In this lesson you will learn <b>useful strategies and advice</b> to answer multiple choice questions in IELTS Listening test most effectively. You will also practice gained skills by answering tricky exercises with multiple choice questions.
The transcript is provided for each audio. The correct answers are underlined in the transcripts. For the examples the transcript is shown, and for the exercises it is hidden. You can hide/show the transcripts as you wish.
First, let’s learn some basic answering strategies and look at the examples below.
</string>
    <string name="tipsReadingQstnCarefully"><b><u>Tips: To avoid such mistakes, make sure you:</u></b></string>
    <string name="tip1ReadingQstn">1. Write words if you’re asked to write words, and write numbers if you’re asked to write numbers.</string>
    <string name="tip2ReadingQstn">2. Don’t exceed the word limit.</string>
    <string name="tip3ReadingQstn">3. Answer the question with relevant information</string>
    <string name="strategy1"><b><u>Strategy 1: don’t immediately pick up the first answer choice you hear.</u></b>
You will often hear all of the answer choices in the audio. And only one of them is correct, the other two are meant to confuse you! So don’t straightaway choose the answer you hear the first as it may be incorrect. So listen carefully and wait until the speaker finishes giving information about the current question.
Let’s try to use this strategy in the first example.
</string>
    <string name="strategy2"><b><u>Strategy 2: know that answers may come in a different order.</u>
    Unlike other questions types in IELTS Listening, multiple choice questions don’t necessarily have their answer choices
        coming in the same order as you hear them in the audio. So don’t worry if you first hear the third answer choice
        - it doesn’t mean you’ve missed the previous two, as answers often come in a different order.
    </b></string>

    <string name="strategy3"><b><u>Strategy 3:  mind that answers are often paraphrased..</u>
   You shouldn’t be waiting for a 100% match - the answer choice can differ from what you hear as it can be paraphrased.
        To approach multiple choice questions effectively, look through the answer choices while listening to the question
        being discussed. Do it to get a general idea of answer choices.
    </b></string>

    <string name="explanationMCQ1"><b>Answer is incorrect</b>\n<b>Explanation:</b> As you can hear, all three answer choices were mentioned.
        However, the first two of them (“all alone” and “sitting on the ground”) are clearly incorrect,
        because the speakers say that people often think that if a bird is all alone or sitting on the ground it
        needs to be rescued, but it’s just learning to fly. The last sentence the speaker says gives us the correct answer:
        “So we should emphasize that people should only attempt to rescue a bird that’s clearly injured”.
        So the correct answer is <b>C.</b></string>

    <string name="explanationMCQ2"><b>Explanation:</b>Moreover, the synonyms are used! The speaker gives the correct answer
        when she says, “In fact, the best way of protection is preventing the disease by keeping yourself clean and washing
        hands before you eat”. But instead of keeping yourself clean or washing hands we have a paraphrased answer choice
        - following hygiene rules. So, the right answer is <b>A</b>.Beware that paraphrase is often used in such questions,
        so you shouldn’t always look for an exact match.</string>

    <string-array name="tfActionName">
        <item>Useful Tips</item>
        <item>Passage 1</item>
        <item>Passage 2</item>
        <item>Passage 3</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="tfPassagesList">
        <item>More than ten years ago, while taking the temperature of the universe, astronomers found something odd.
            They discovered that a patch of sky, spanning the width of 20 moons, was unusually cold.
            The astronomers were measuring the thermal radiation that bathes the entire universe,
            a glowing relic of the big bang.To gaze at this cosmic microwave background,
            or CMB, is to glimpse the primordial1 universe, a time when it was less than 400,000 years old.
            The CMB blankets the sky, and looks pretty much the same everywhere,
            existing at a feebly cold temperature of 2.725 kelvins -
            just a couple degrees warmer than absolute zero.
            But armed with the newly launched WMAP satellite,
            the astronomers had set out to probe temperature variations as tiny as one part in 100,000.
            Born from the quantum froth that was the universe a half-moment after the big bang,
            those random fluctuations help scientists understand what the cosmos is made of and how it all came to be.</item>
        <item>According to the Met Office, the UK had its warmest July day ever on July 1, when temperatures hit 36.7 C near London.
            There were record heat waves in many countries including Spain, while the African continent had the second-warmest July
            on record. While the impact of increased levels of carbon dioxide in the atmosphere is a key driver of rising
            temperatures, another important factor is El Nino. This natural phenomenon, which appears as a large swathe of warm
            water in the Pacific every few years, is known to push up global temperatures. In recent days there have been reports
            that this year\'s El Nino will be particularly intense. As a result, many experts believe that 2015 will be the warmest
            year on record by some margin. The seas have also been soaking up a large amount of heat, the NOAA said, with record
            warming in large expanses of the Pacific and Indian Oceans Peter Stott, head of climate monitoring and attribution at
            the UK Met Office, said: \"A strong El Nino is under way in the tropical Pacific and this, combined with the long-term
            global warming trend, means there is the potential to see some very warm months throughout this year - as the new
            figures for July appear to show\".
        </item>
        <item>
            The standard stereotype among Americans is that Canadians are like Americans, except they say \'eh\' a lot and pronounce \'out and about\' as \'oot and aboot\'. Many Canadians, on the other hand, will tell you that Canadian English is more like British English, and as proof will hold aloft the spellings colour and centre and the name zed for the letter Z.
  Canadian does exist as a separate variety of British English, with subtly distinctive features of pronunciation and vocabulary. It has its own dictionaries; the Canadian Press has its own style guide; the Editors\' Association of Canada has just released a second edition of Editing Canadian English. But an emblematic feature of Editing Canadian English is comparison tables of American versus British spellings so the Canadian editor can come to a reasonable decision on which to use… on each occasion. The core of Canadian English is a pervasive ambivalence.
  Canadian history helps to explain this. In the beginning there were the indigenous people, with far more linguistic and cultural variety than Europe. They\'re still there, but Canadian English, like Canadian Anglophone society in general, gives them little more than desultory token nods. Fights between European settlers shaped Canadian English more. The French, starting in the 1600s, colonised the St Lawrence River region and the Atlantic coast south of it. In the mid-1700s, England got into a war with France, concluding with the Treaty of Paris in 1763, which ceded \'New France\' to England. The English allowed any French to stay who were willing to become subjects of the English King.
  At the time of the Treaty of Paris, however, there were very few English speakers in Canada. The American Revolution changed that. The founding English-speaking people of Canada were United Empire Loyalists – people who fled American independence and were rewarded with land in Canada. Thus, Canadian English was, from its very beginning, both American – because its speakers had come from the American colonies – and not American, because they rejected the newly independent nation.
  Just as the Americans sought to have a truly distinct, independent American version of English, the loyalists sought to remain more like England… sort of. These were people whose variety of English was already diverging from the British and vice versa: when the residents of London and its environs began to drop their r\'s and change some of their vowels people in certain parts of the United States adopted some of these changes, but Canadians did not. </item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="details">
        <item><b>IELTS</b>- International English Language Testing System: It is widely recognized as
            a standard of testing the language ability of candidates who need to study or work where English
            is used as a medium of communication. It is owned by three partners: the University of Cambridge -
            LIFE ESOL Examinations, the British Council and the IDP: Education Australia.
            <n><b>Test Format</b></n>
            IELTS consists of six modules. All candidates take the same Listening and Speaking modules.
            There is a choice of – Reading and Writing modules to whether an examinee is taking the Academic
            or the General version of the Test.
            <b>Academic</b>: For candidates taking the test for entry to undergraduate or postgraduate studies
            or for professional reasons.
            <b>General Training</b>: For candidates taking the test for entry to vocational or training programs
            not at degree level, for admission secondary schools and for immigration purposes.
            The test modules are taken in the following order:
            <n><b><u>LISTENING</u></b></n>
            <b>4 sections, 40 items, approximately 30 minutes </b>(additional 10 minutes to transfer the answers on an answer sheet)
             <n><b><u>ACADEMIC READING:</u></b></n>
            <b>3 passages, 40 items, 60 minutes</b>
            or, <n><b><u>GENERAL TRAINING READING: </u></b></n>
            <b>3 sections, 40 items, 60 minutes</b>
            <n><b><u>ACADEMIC WRITING:</u></b></n>
            <b>2 tasks, 60 minutes</b>
            or, <n><b><u>GENERAL TRAINING WRITING:</u></b></n>
            <b>2 tasks, 60 minutes</b>


            <n><u><b></b>SPEAKING:</u></n>
            <b>11 -14 minutes</b>
            <b><u>Total test time: 2 hours 44 minutes</u></b>
        </item>
        <item>
            <n><b>Paper format:</b></n>
            There are four sections with ten questions each. The questions are designed so that the answers
            appear in the order they are heard in the audio. The first two sections deal with situations set
            in everyday social contexts. In Section 1, there is a conversation between two speakers
            (for example, a conversation about travel arrangements), and in Section 2, there is a monologue
            in (for example, a speech about local facilities). The final two sections deal with situations set
            in educational and training contexts. In Section 3, there is a conversation between two main speakers
            (for example, two university students in discussion, perhaps guided by a tutor), and in Section 4,
            there is a monologue on an academic subject. The recordings are heard only once. They include a range
            of accents, including British, Australian, New Zealand, American and Canadian
            <b>Timing:</b> Approximately 30 minutes (plus 10 minutes transfer time)
            <b>No. of questions:</b> 40



            <b>Task types:</b>
            A variety of question types are used chosen from the following:

            •	multiple choice
            •	matching
            •	plan/map/diagram labeling
            •	form/note/table/flow-chart/summary completion
            •	Sentence completion.
            <b>Answering System</b>
            Test takers write their answers on the question paper as they listen and at the end of the test are given
            10 minutes to transfer their answers to an answer sheet. Care should be taken when writing answers on the
            answer sheet as poor spelling and grammar are penalized.

        </item>
        <item>
           <n><b>Paper format:</b></n>
            There are three reading passages with a variety of questions using a number of task types.
            <b><n>Task types:</n></b>
            A variety of question types are used, chosen from the following; multiple choice,
            identifying information, identifying the writer’s views/claims, matching information,
            matching headings, matching features, matching sentence endings, sentence completion,
            summary completion, note completion, table completion, flow-chart completion, diagram label completion
            and short-answer questions.
            <b><n>Sources</n></b>
            Texts are taken from books, journals, magazines and newspapers, and have been written for a non-specialist audience.
            All the topics are of general interest. They deal with issues which are interesting,
            recognizably appropriate and accessible to test takers entering undergraduate or postgraduate courses
            or seeking professional registration. The passages may be written in a variety of styles, for example narrative,
            descriptive or discursive/argumentative. At least one text contains detailed logical argument.
            Texts may contain non-verbal materials such as diagrams, graphs or illustrations.
            If texts contain technical terms a simple glossary is provided.
            <b><n>Answering</n></b>
            Test takers are required to transfer their answers to an answer sheet during the time allowed for the test.
            No extra time is allowed for transfer. Care should be taken when writing answers on the answer sheet as poor
            spelling and grammar are penalized.

            <n>Marks: Each question is worth 1 mark.</n>

        </item>
        <item>
           <n><b>Paper format:</b></n>
            <n>There are two Writing tasks and BOTH must be completed.
            Task types: In Task 1, test takers are asked to describe some visual information
            (graph/table/chart/diagram) in their own words. They need to write 150 words in about 20 minutes.
            In Task 2, they respond to a point of view or argument or problem. They need to write 250 words
            in about 40 minutes.</n>
            <b>Answering:</b>
            <n>
            Answers must be given on the answer sheet and must be written in full.
            Notes or bullet points are not acceptable as answers. Test takers may write on the question paper
            but this cannot be taken from the examination room and will not be seen by the examiner.</n>
        Marks: <b>Band score 9 on individual task, from task 1, 40% marks and from task 2,
            60% marks will be counted and then, both are summed to get a overall band in writing.</b>
        </item>
        <item>
            <n><b>Paper format:</b></n>
            The Speaking test consists of an oral interview between the test takers and an examiner.
            All Speaking tests are recorded.
            <b>Task types:</b>
            <n>There are three parts to the test and each part fulfils a specific function in terms of interaction pattern,
            task input and test takers output.In part one, examiner asks some basic questions about candidates - name, interest
            etc. In the second part, candidates will get an cue card, then s/he will have to talk about the topic on the
            cue card for around 2 minutes. There will be some time to jot down some notes about the given topic.Finally, in the
            last part, examiner will ask about more abstract issues which are thematically linked to topic in part 2. Total time
            for speaking test is approximately 15-20 minutes.</n>
            Marks: test takers are scored on the basis of band score 9.

        </item>
        <item>
            <n><b>Listening Score calculation</b></n>
            <n>Listenig scores are calculated by the number of correct answers a candidate scores out of 40 questions. No
            point loss for wrong answers.</n>
            <n><b>Correct answers    -     Band Scores</b></n>
            <n><b>   39-40           -     9          </b></n>
            <n><b>   37-38           -     8.5          </b></n>
            <n><b>   35-36           -     8          </b></n>
            <n><b>   32-34           -     7.5         </b></n>
            <n><b>   30-31           -     7          </b></n>
            <n><b>   26-29           -     6.5         </b></n>
            <n><b>   23-25           -     6          </b></n>
            <n><b>   18-22           -     5.5          </b></n>
            <n><b>   16-17           -     5           </b></n>
            <n><b>   13-15           -     4.5          </b></n>
            <n><b>   11-12           -     4          </b></n>
            <n><b>   8-10            -     3.5          </b></n>
            <n><b>   6-7             -     3          </b></n>
            <n><b>   3-5             -     2.5          </b></n>

            <n><b>Reading Score calculation</b></n>
            <n>Readnig scores are also calculated by the number of correct answers a candidate scores out of 40 questions. No
            point loss for wrong answers.</n>
            <n><b>Correct answers    -     Band Scores</b></n>
            <n><b>   39-40           -     9          </b></n>
            <n><b>   37-38           -     8.5          </b></n>
            <n><b>   35-36           -     8          </b></n>
            <n><b>   33-34           -     7.5         </b></n>
            <n><b>   30-32           -     7          </b></n>
            <n><b>   27-29           -     6.5         </b></n>
            <n><b>   23-26           -     6          </b></n>
            <n><b>   19-22           -     5.5          </b></n>
            <n><b>   15-18           -     5           </b></n>
            <n><b>   13-14           -     4.5          </b></n>
            <n><b>   10-12           -     4          </b></n>
            <n><b>   8-9             -     3.5          </b></n>
            <n><b>   6-7             -     3          </b></n>
            <n><b>   3-5             -     2.5          </b></n>

        <b>Band score: </b> All IELTS scores from 0 to 9. In each skill, candidates get score and then have an overview bandscore
            which is the avarage of all scores.

        </item>

    </string-array>
</resources>
